Oh, hey, Ross.
I'm so glad
someone's here.
Could you zip me up?
Uh... sure.
Thank you.
Can you believe no one
between my
apartment and here
offered to do that for me?
People.
So, uh... why are you
so dressed up?
Oh, um, Mike's picking
me up for a date.
Oh, yeah? Now,
how is that going?
Is it getting serious?
Oh, I don't know,
I don't know.
I mean, you know,
I like him...
but, you know,
am I ready
to take my Grade A loins
off the meat market?
I'm not quite sure.
Yeah.
You know, I really admire
your whole dating attitude.
It's so healthy.
I'm always, like,
"Is this moving too fast?
"Is this moving too slow?
Where is this going?"
Yeah, I know. You are
a bit of a drama queen.
Well, you, you're so
much better off, you know.
You just go from guy to guy
having fun and not worrying
that it never turns
into anything serious.
I wouldn't say "never."
You know, there
was that guy.
Okay, well, what about...?
Okay, well, there's
got to be someone.
There isn't.
That's what I'm saying.
Oh, my God, you're right.
I know, and yet, here you are,
all ready for the next date.
I can't believe I never
realized this before.
I'm in my 30s, and
I've never been
in a long-term
relationship?
Oh, my God! What's
wrong with me?
No, no-no. No. Uh...
There's, there's
nothing wrong with you.
I mean, you don't strike me
as the type of person
that wants
to get married anyway.
I want to get married.
Oh, my God, please, please
don't cry because of me.
Phebes, I don't know
what I'm talking about.
I've been divorced three times.
Yeah, well, at least
you've been married.
Oh, my God, I want to
trade lives with Ross?
Phoebe.
What's wrong?
Nothing. I'm excited
about our date.
Mike, this is Ross Geller.
Ross, this is Mike... ( sobs)
I'm sorry,
I didn't catch your...
It's Mike Hanigan.
Oh, Ross Geller.
Hey.
Uh, so are you sure
you're ready to go?
Uh-huh.
How do I look?
Do you have a compact
in your purse?
No.
You look great.
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Hey, Joey.
Hey.
This girl
won't turn around.
I can't tell whether
she's hot or not.
What do you think?
Joey, I am not going
to objectify women with you.
but if her face is as nice
as her ass, whoo, mama.
All right, thanks.
Oh, hey, have you talked
to Chandler?
Yeah, he has to stay
in Tulsa this weekend.
How come?
I don't know-- he has to work.
There's some big rush on the...
Uh...
Damn it, one of these days I'm
going to have to start listening
when he talks about his job.
Yeah. Oh, hey, why don't you
fly out there and surprise him?
Maybe I will go.
Yeah. We'll have a
little second honeymoon
at the Tulsa Ramada.
Oh, and you now what
you should bring?
Your black, see-through teddy
with the attached garters.
How do you know
I have one of those?
Didn't until just now.
Ugh. Hot... not hot.
Hot.
Excuse me?
Uh...
I said that I think you're hot
and, uh, now I'm embarrassed.
Oh, I thought you said, "Hi."
That would have been better.
I'll try that.
Hi.
I'm Joey.
I'm Hayley.
Oh. Uh, look,
I don't normally ask out women
that I meet in coffee houses.
Ha!
Gesundheit.
But, uh...
I would love to go out with you.
Really?
Great.
Did I... did I actually ask you?
Oh, um, that's just where
you were going.
I figured I'd help you out.
You don't seem like the kind
of guy who does this a lot.
Ha!
Seriously, Gunther, you should
see someone about that cold.
If it gets much worse,
you could die.
So how'd the date go?
Well, it was awful.
Every time I thought
about what you said
I started crying.
So he hasn't called?
Would you call this girl?
( sobbing ):
Thanks for...
a lovely... evening.
Oh. Now I feel terrible.
This is all my fault.
Well, you know what
you should feel terrible about?
This could have been
my serious guy.
He was... he was sweet
and smart and funny.
Do you know how hard it is
to meet a guy like that?
We are a rare breed.
What a great dinner!
Yeah, and, hey
thanks again for letting me have
that last piece of cake
at the restaurant.
( laughing )
You're welcome, again.
I'm going to go
make some coffee.
Can I get you anything?
Uh... do you have any cake?
( laughing )
So, this is going pretty good.
Dinner was nice.
We've got a lot in common.
Mmm. Victoria's Secret.
Huh.
We even like the same books.
Ooh.
There's a scary painting.
Wait a minute.
I think I've been scared
by that painting before.
You know what?
This whole place looks familiar.
I have definitely been
in this apartment.
I know I've seen
this weird plant before.
Ow.
It did that the last time.
Oh, my God, I've gone out
with this girl before.
Yeah. We had sex on this couch
and then on that chair and...
No, wait, we didn't do it here.
Which is weird because it seems
like a perfectly good place.
Ow. That's why.
( knocking )
Hey, Mike. Uh...
sorry to just drop by like this.
Can I come in?
Sure.
Who are you?
Uh, I'm-I'm Ross.
Phoebe's friend
f-from the coffee house.
Yeah.
Yeah, I really,
really need
to talk to you
about something.
Okay.
Unless... you're not
going to try to get me
to join a cult, are you?
No.
Oh. No, it's just...
You have that look.
Damn Super Cuts.
What's up?
Is Phoebe okay?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
No. Oh, Phoebe is great
but, um...
I'm an idiot. Okay? Look.
Right before you
guys went out
I accidentally
got her all upset.
Oh. That's why she was weird.
Yes. Yeah.
I-I said something stupid
about her never having had
a serious relationship
but you should know
she is so much fun,
a wonderful person.
Please, don't blow her off.
I'm not going to blow her off.
I actually just got off
the phone with her.
We're going out tomorrow night.
I hope that's okay with you...
stranger from the coffee house.
Well, then,
I-I didn't need to bother you.
You... or the four other
Mike Hanigans I bothered.
Hey, wait, wait,
wait, wait.
Is that true what you said?
That Phoebe's never had
a serious relationship?
Of course she has.
If she's never had
a serious relationship
do you think I'd
go around broadcasting it
like some kind of...
unstoppable moron?
But you did say it.
Yes. Yes, I did.
And I will also say...
what I'm about to say
vis-a-vis... the following.
Phoebe has never had
a serious relationship
since...
her super-serious relationship
with.... Vikram.
Vikram?
What? That's a real name!
♪ Oklahoma, where the wind ♪
♪ Comes sweeping
down the plain... ♪
Stop it!
Why couldn't they
have sent me to Texas?
7:00.
Maybe I'll hit the gym.
Oh... who am I kidding?
Pay-Per-View porn.
Do not disturb! Do not disturb!
Surprise!
Monica.
Is everything all right?
Yeah, everything's great.
I was just watching
some regular television there.
Oh, what a... what
a pleasant surprise.
I'm going to go
freshen up, okay?
Okay, honey.
Ooh. That was close.
( phone ringing )
Hello.
Hey, Rache, it's me.
Okay, I just got
to Chandler's room
and I caught him...
molesting himself.
Oh. That couldn't
have been pretty
but you know, guys do that.
Yeah? Well, the weird part is...
he was getting off
to a shark-attack show.
No.
Yes. Chandler
watches shark porn.
While watching sharks?
Uh-huh.
Are you sure that's what
he was doing?
Do you know how many times
I've seen him jump up like that?
Believe me, I know
what he was doing.
Oh, man... sharks.
I know.
I always knew there was
something weird about that dude.
But you promised to love him
no matter what.
"What" means like
if he gets a disease
or kills someone.
Not if he gets his jollies
to Jaws.
You know what,
though, honey
guys are just
different.
They like things
that we can't understand.
You know,
I once dated
this guy who wanted to pretend
that he was an archaeologist
and that I was
this naughty cave woman
who he unfroze
from a block of ice.
( chuckles )
Ooh, are you talking
about my brother?
Yeah, I didn't disguise that
very well, did I?
Hey.
Hi.
Listen
to this:
I went out
with this girl last night.
Halfway through our date
I realized
I already slept
with her.
So basically
you've slept
with all the women
in New York
and now you're just
going around again?
Yeah, but that's not even
the weird part.
I don't think she remembered
sleeping with me!
Like you don't remember
sleeping with her.
But she should remember
sleeping with me.
I am very memorable.
You guys know.
How do we know?!
We've never slept
with you.
And whose fault is that?
What's the big deal?
You forgot, she forgot.
Maybe you were having
an off night.
Hey!
I never have an off night, okay
although sometimes
if I'm a little bloated
I don't feel that sexy
but even then,
I'm better than most.
Honey, why don't you
just let it go
and ask her out again?
Yeah, you're both
so slutty
you don't even remember
who you slept with.
You're made
for each other.
Oh, interesting.
Yeah.
All right, well,
I'll go out with her again
and I'll try
to get past it. Yeah.
Oh, salt! Bloating!
Joey, Joey
What?
you don't think
sharks are sexy, do you?
No.
Wait a minute--
what was the Little Mermaid?
( knock on door )
It's open!
Hey.
Hey... Michael--
we're going out again. Yay!
Yay!
Quick thing-- I went
to talk to Mike.
What?
What... what did you...
what did you do, Ross?
Oh, boy-- you got
mad at that part.
I-I...
I went over there,
you know, to tell him
how great
you are, but...
well, you know me...
blah-blah-blah-blah-blah-blah.
And I ended up
telling him, um, that...
What?
Um, you had
a six-year-long relationship
with a guy named Vikram.
What? Why?
Well, he seemed
to bum hard
when I told him
you'd never been
in a serious relationship.
If you hadn't just had a baby
with my best friend
I swear to Lucifer...
a rabid dog would be feasting
on your danglers right now.
Well, Phoeb, I think
you'll feel differently
when you know a little bit
about Vikram.
Okay...
he's um...
he's a kite designer.
And he used to date Oprah.
No, I'm not going along
with some lie
you made up, Ross.
No, I'm just going
to be honest with him.
Good.
Yeah, just be
honest with him.
Yeah, I have nothing
to be ashamed of.
No.
Okay, so, all right
I haven't been
in a relationship
that lasted longer
than a month.
Okay, I-I-I haven't had
a real boyfriend.
You know,
if he can't handle it
then he can leave.
Which he will.
And, you know...
that's...
okay, so I'll just be
alone forever.
You know,
it'll be fine.
It'll be fine.
I'll go on walking tours
with widows and lesbians.
( knock on door )
Oh...
I'll get it.
Okay.
You know, I'm trying to remember
the last time I opened a door
and you weren't there.
Phoebe
are you okay?
Hm-mm, yeah.
Yeah, there's just, um...
Uh... there's something
you should know.
Vikram just called.
So it was really
a shock
after 25 years
of marriage
my parents--
the perfect couple--
getting divorced.
I took it the hardest
'cause I was youngest.
Hm-mm, hm-mm, sure, yeah.
How can you not remember me?!
What?
How could you not remember
that we slept together?
What? When?
I don't know.
I really, really think
I would remember
sleeping with you.
Come on, come on,
search your brain, all right?
It was... a certain amount
of time ago.
Okay,
I was here.
You were here.
We had sex... here...
here... here...
Not there.
Anything?
No, it's not ringing
any bells.
My God, woman!
How many people do you have
to have been with
not to remember any of this?
Hey, Hayley.
We really got to fix
that doorknob.
Joey?
Oh...
I slept with you.
And you obviously remember me.
Hey, I still got it!
So we're good.
I'll let myself out.
And I said,
"Okay, Vikram
"you can't just call
every time
"you get lonely,
you know.
You-you gave up that
right when you slept
with Rachel."
Wait, Rachel--
I thought she just
had a baby with Ross.
Yeah... well... yeah.
You know, but Emma's
birth certificate
might say "Geller"
but her eyes
say "Mukherjee."
God, that is so wrong.
And on top of that,
he's a glue sniffer?
Hmm. I know
but he calls,
and my heart goes to him.
You know, that bastard
is one smooth-talking
freelance kite designer.
I just think there's somebody
better out there for you.
You know,
I'm not saying me but...
Maybe me.
Oh.
And you don't have to worry
about glue sniffing with me.
Although I do smell
the occasional Magic Marker.
Yeah, uh, anyway, I just...
I think I can make you happy.
Okay, I can't
do this.
What's wrong?
Well, there
is no Vikram.
Ross made him up
because I-I...
I really never have been in
a long-term relationship.
I've never... I've never
lived with a guy.
I've never even
celebrated an
anniversary, so...
you know, if that's... if
that's too weird for you
and-and you want to leave,
I totally understand.
In fact, I'll close my eyes
and make it less awkward.
You kissed me.
Uh-huh.
So you don't think
I'm a total freak.
No...
well...
Look, can I...
can I think
you're a little weird
and also cool
for telling me the truth
and also want to kiss you?
I guess so.
Can I... can I think it's
cool that you kissed me
and also wanted
to kiss you again?
And, um, be
a little concerned
about the Magic Markers?
Oh, definitely.
( phone ringing )
( beep )
( Ross with Indian accent):
This is Vikram.
Hi, honey.
I'm home.
Hi.
How was your flight?
Oh, it was great.
Here, why don't
you sit down.
Get yourself comfortable.
Because I have a little...
surprise for you.
Well, well, well.
Must be 5:00 in Tulsa
'cause it's sex o'clock
in NYC.
Okay...
This is how much
I love you.
Honey...
why am I watching a bunch
of sharks swimming around?
Oh, is this... is this
not the good part?
Do you want me
to fast-forward
to something... toothier?
No, I'm just not sure
that you got the right
movie, that's all.
Oh, this is the only one
they had at our video store.
But they did have something
called Crocodile Killers.
Or does it always have
to be sharks?
Does what always
have to be sharks?
Honey, look
we could do something else.
Do you want me to get
into the tub
and thrash?
What's going on?
Sweetie, it's okay.
It's okay.
I still love you.
Let me be a part of this.
I saw what you were
doing in Tulsa.
Angry sharks turn you on.
No, they don't.
Then why were you watching them
and giving yourself a treat?
Oh, my God.
When you came in,
I switched the channel.
I was just watching
regular porn.
Really?
Yes, just some
good old-fashioned
American
girl-on-girl action.
I cannot tell you how
happy that makes me.
Oh, honey.
( chuckles )
You are an amazing wife.
No, really. You are amazing.
I mean, you were actually
going to do this for me?
I mean, where do you find
the strength
and the understanding
for something like that?
I'm very, very
drunk right now.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
See, ordinarily
I would talk to her
but my confidence
is shaken.
Did I sleep with her,
did I not sleep with her?
You know, maybe this
is a wake-up call.
You know, about your
whole dating attitude.
You're in your 30s,
and you have never been
in a long-term
relationship.
You know, you go
from woman to woman
meaningless experience,
to meaningless experience.
Never even worrying
that it doesn't turn
into something
more serious.
You're right.
I love my life.
Actually,
did sleep with her.